<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel><title>No Breadcrumbs</title><link>http://nobreadcrumbs.github.io</link>
<description></description><language>en</language>
<lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 00:47:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 00:47:57 +0000</pubDate>
<atom:link href="http://nobreadcrumbs.github.io/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
<item><title>
How I Made A No Breadcrumbs Blog
</title><description><![CDATA[

<p>Good morning/afternoon/evening.</p>

<p>I want to tell you how I made a “No Breadcrumbs” blog, and by that I mean I’ve made this blog without a trace, I think.</p>

<p>Before we begin, let me tell you a little about what I was used.</p>

<ul>
<li>USB Stick (4GB, but I would prefer if it was 8GB)</li>
<li>Ubuntu Live CD</li>
<li><a href="https://tails.boum.org/">Tails OS</a></li>
<li><a href="https://bitcoin.org/en/">Bitcoins</a></li>
</ul>

<p>Let’s begin.</p>

<p>I bought bitcoins via an anonymous <a href="https://localbitcoins.com/">LocalBitcoins.com</a> account, using <a href="https://www.torproject.org/">Tor</a> ( which I will discuss later). I found a seller who was willing to negotiate with me using PGP encrypted messages. We agreed on a time and place where I would put money. I confirmed in advance that there were no surveillance cameras nearby, and put the money in the drop. Within eight hours, the bitcoins were released from the escrow service. I then used my Bitcoins to buy a laptop and a USB stick.</p>

<p>I dissected the laptop and confirmed that there were no hardware keyloggers installed inside. I then proceeded to insert a Ubuntu Live CD and booted into Linux. I then downloaded and installed the <a href="https://tails.boum.org/">Tails operating system</a> on my USB key.</p>

<p><a href="https://tails.boum.org/">Tails</a> is a Debian operating system mainly centered around anonymity. It forces all network connections through the Tor network. The Tor network is simply a large amount of “nodes” that transfer encrypted web traffic between each other to hide the identity of a user. <a href="https://tails.boum.org/">Tails</a> also securely wipes the RAM of the computer it is used on, and keeps the files you ask it to keep (that are stored on an encrypted partition).</p>

<p>I started <a href="https://tails.boum.org/">Tails</a> and configured the encrypted volume. On this I stored my Bitcoin keypairs, this blog, and a KeePass database. KeePass can generate passwords which are very strong and I  make sure they each have at least 400 bits of entropy.</p>

<p>I then made an email account on <a href="https://www.safe-mail.net/">safe-mail.net</a>, and used it to make a GitHub account. After trying several times to configure <a href="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</a>, <a href="http://docs.getpelican.com/en/3.3.0/">Pelican</a>, <a href="http://zespia.tw/hexo/">Hexo</a> and <a href="http://www.cabinjs.com/">Cabin</a>, I finally decided to use a simple static site generator (made in shell) to generate my blog. I chose <a href="https://github.com/cfenollosa/bashblog">bashblog</a>. I’ll write a post, push it to GitHub and it will live at nobreadcrumbs.github.io!</p>

<p>How could my identity be compromised?</p>

<p><strong>Option 1: DNS leaks of any kind</strong></p>

<p>I access the Web from a public place, and route traffic through my two VPNs. I also check forDNS leaks when I access the Internet. The furthest someone couold get with this method is what is the IP of the public place from which I access the Internet, which provides no information because I never go to the same place twice.</p>

<p><strong>Option 2: My Vocabulary</strong></p>

<p>You might think you can identify me by analyzing my vocabulary. To prevent this, I find synonyms for each word that I use, and run my posts through many layers of Google Translate. It goes something like this: English &gt;&gt;&gt; Foreign Language &gt;&gt;&gt; English (I corrected all errors) &gt;&gt;&gt; Foreign Language 2… Up to six different layers. I got this idea from UntraceableBlog.com (it was the last piece in my mission , thank you for that!) :)</p>

<p><strong>Option 3: Identifying me Through my Bitcoin Dead Drop</strong></p>

<p>I lied at the beginning of this post. <strong>I</strong> did not put the money in the dead drop. I met a friend, told them to put money there, and I left without a trace.</p>

<p><strong>Option 4: A kind of other attack</strong></p>

<p>It is unlikely that there has been another attack because of steps I have taken above.</p>

<p>I hope that you learned something about anonymity, and maybe you can create an anonymous blog, too! I’ll probably use this blog to something else in the future. Until then, goodbye!</p>
<!-- text end -->
]]></description><link>http://nobreadcrumbs.github.io/how-i-made-a-no-breadcrumbs-blog.html</link>
<guid>http://nobreadcrumbs.github.io/how-i-made-a-no-breadcrumbs-blog.html</guid>
<dc:creator>nobreadcrumbs</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 00:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item>
</channel></rss>
